russianremote.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy - Russianremote.com

This Website Privacy Policy describes RussianRemote.com's collection and use of information from visitors to our websites and to our online store (together, our website). By using our website, you agree with the terms of this Website Privacy Policy.

**Changes to Website Privacy Policy**  
This Website Privacy Policy will be changed from time-to-time. When we make a change to our service Privacy Policy, we will (1) notify you by email that our service Privacy Policy has been changed, (2) place a prominent notice on our website, (3) change the last updated date at the top, and (4) post the changed Website Privacy Policy at http://rurem.com/privacy-policy.

**How We Collect Personally Identifiable Information**  
There are two ways we collect personally identifiable information: (1) information which you supply to us directly; and (2) information which we gather from your computer using cookies.

“Cookies” are small files or records that we place on your computer’s hard drive to collect information about your activities on our website. The cookies transmit this information back to the computers at our service; these computers are the only computers which are authorized to read such information. The information captured makes it possible for us (1) to speed your visit, keep track of items in your shopping cart, and provide you with recommendations for content; (2) to remember information you gave to us so you don’t have to reenter it each time you visit our website; and (3) to monitor the total number of visitors and pages viewed. Most people do not know that cookies are being placed on their computers when they visit our website or most websites because browsers are typically set to accept cookies. You can choose to have your browser warn you every time a cookie is being sent to you or you can turn off cookie placement. If your browser is not enabled to accept cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of our website.

**When We Collect Information and the Types of Information We Collect**  
The information we collect will depend on what you do when you visit our site.

When you visit our site:  
When you visit our site, our servers automatically log the information provided in the HTTP request header including the Internet Protocol number (IP Address of the computer or router you requested the page from), the time of the request, the URL of your request, and other information that is provided in the HTTP header. We use all of this information to measure visits to our website and how our website is being used. We also use this information to improve our websites performance and layout and to assess the preferences for our content options and features.

However, unless you visit our store, we do not collect personally identifiable information including your name, email address, billing address, shipping address, phone number or credit card information or any information about content you may select or download or memberships you may purchase.

**When You Visit our Online Store**  
Each subscriber to our Service will be supplied with a personal home page at the store login. When you set up your account in our online store, you are asked to create and secure access to your home page by supplying us with a unique User Name and Password. You will also be asked to supply us with personally identifiable information, including your name, billing address, mailing address, telephone numbers, email address and credit card information. We will collect and maintain all of that information and any other information you provide to us in the future through our online store for the purpose of account management, billing and collections, customer support and service management and to provide you and us with a constant source of information about the status of your account, payments, licenses to content and memberships and subscriptions.

We also use cookies to gather information about your visits to your store.our our online store Home Page, including your browsing visits and selections and the time and duration of your visit. We collect this information for the purpose of monitoring interest in our content offerings, use of our website and to improve navigation on our website.

**When You Order Content, Subscriptions or Memberships**  
RussianRemote.com includes a shopping cart through which you may place orders for content, subscriptions, memberships, merchandise and any updates to the our service Receiver or any future hardware which enables access to the Service.

Using a combination of cookies and information you supply directly through our online store, we collect information about your use of the store.our service/login.cfm website for the purposes of creating billing statements and maintaining customer accounts, customer support, targeted recommendations of content to you and managing the operation of the Service. The personally identifiable information collected includes items such as:

Information about your transactions with us, including the specific services we provide to you, the content you select, download or view, charges for content, and your payments to us.

Information about your transactions with us, including the specific services we provide to you, the content you select, download or view, charges for content, and your payments to us.

**Memberships and subscription status and changes.**  
All account information, including your name, billing address, mailing address, telephone numbers, email address and credit card information.

We may aggregate anonymous information about your use of the Service, your content download activity, your membership and subscription purchases and your browsing activity on our website and deliver this information to our content partners and licensors for the purpose of providing them with an assessment of interest in their content.

**How We Protect Personally Identifiable Information**  
We employ measures designed to limit access to the personally identifiable information we collect to those employees or others who need access to it in order to conduct business and service your account. Our employees are required to maintain and protect the confidentiality of personal information, must follow established procedures to do so, and are subject to disciplinary action if they fail to do so. In addition, we maintain reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect personally identifiable information. Finally, companies we hire to provide support services to us are not permitted to use personally identifiable information for their own purposes and are contractually obligated to maintain strict confidentiality. We limit their use of your information to the performance of the specific services that we have requested from them.

You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your User Name and Password for your our online store Home Page and for ensuring that no minors or third parties access or use in any way your our service account.

**Our Personally Identifiable Information Disclosure Policy**  
Other than the limited circumstances described in this Website Privacy Policy or as permitted or required by law, our service does not share personally identifiable information with third parties. However, we may occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including credit card billing and processing, collections, network hosting, mailing, advertising and marketing, and deliveries. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

In addition, our service will not disclose your personally identifiable information, unless we are required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on our service or our website; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of our service, our content partners and licensors, licensors of certain intellectual property and our creditors (in the event of a dissolution proceeding), and, (3) address circumstances affecting the personal safety of users of our service, our website, or the public. In the event our service goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Privacy Options For Customers**  
We believe that the information that our service collects is necessary to ensure the proper account billing, management and operation of the Service. If you do not wish to have this information collected, your only option is to terminate your use of the Service.

Our service may send out periodic email messages to you informing you of technical service issues related to the Service or your our service account. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the Service you have chosen. our service may also contact you by telephone with service or account related inquiries or information.

Our service may also send out periodic email messages recommending certain content to you based on your previous selections or informing you about promotions for content or content packages. You will have the right to opt out of these messages through an unsubscribe link contained in each email.

**Access To Your Personal Information**  
We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal contact information is correct and current. By visiting your Home Page at our online store, you may Obtain information about your account information and current charges. Verify the accuracy of your account and contact information. Correct or update your account, credit card information and contact information.

Last Updated: October 29, 2009

About it to do product I look and was [viagra generic](http://bestviagraoriginals.com/) professional have stretching stocking acne isn’t, many.
